



**ADDRESS**Via Achille Grandi 24,
Piombino (LI), 57025, Italy



PHONE 389-662-7974



luigidimaio99@gmail.com



LINKEDIN PROFILE
<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/">https://www.linkedin.com/</a>
/in/luigi-dimaio

# **SKILLS**

Fast Learner
Computer Skills
Communication Skills
Ability to Work in a Team
Ability to Multitask
HTML & CSS
JavaScript
Effective Time Management

## **LANGUAGES**

Italian NativeEnglish Upper Intermediate

# LUIGI DI MAIO

Junior Frontend Developer

Piombino, 57025

**%**+39 3896627974

#### **PROFILE**

Hardworking young person with a strong interest in technology and programming and a strong desire to demonstrate their abilities and ideas. Teamwork experience and eagerness to join a new team and assist them as a dedicated and passionate Junior Frontend Developer.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

04/2022 - 04/2022

Ted Talks | Vancouver Convention Center | Vancouver

Vancouver Buffet Server:

- Brought forth a working knowledge of server operating systems.
- Aimed to be reliable, courteous, and professional during guest interactions.
- Made suggestions to customers based on preferences.

05/2022 - 12/2022

Herschel Supply Co. | Gastown | Vancouver

**Retail Associate:** 

- Welcome and assist the customers through the presentation of products efficiently maintaining the highest standards of customer service;
- Manage the checkout operations and execute debit, credit, and cash tenders;
- To use up-selling and cross-selling strategies to achieve sales objectives;
- Ability to remain professional, and enthusiastic during customer and team interactions;

#### **EDUCATION**

2016 - 2021

High School Diploma ISIS Einaudi | Piombino (LI) – Italy

01/2022 - 12/2022

**Diploma in Business Communications** | Greystone College | Vancouver (BC)

<u>Academic Achievement Award:</u> For achieving academic excellence, with a GPA at the top of the class.

#### **INTERNSHIP**

07/2020 - 07/2020

SmartBit Lab | Piombino (LI) - Italy

Customer Service and Computer Maintenance:

 Provided superior customer service to clients by addressing all questions and concerns and a commitment to customer satisfaction.

09/2021 - 10/2021

Future Learning Lab | Erasmus | Vienna

- Served as an everyday pillar of support and assistance to the Head of the office.
- Graded papers and assisted the head teacher with any paperwork, copying, and distribution of assignments or documents.

### **COURSES**

- Responsive Web Design Developer Certification, FreeCodeCamp.org
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification, FreeCodeCamp.org
- Web Marketing certificate, Udemy
- JavaScript for Beginners, Udemy